Finding Aid for William Bolcom and Joan Morris Papers 1960-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
William Bolcom and Joan Morris papers
1960-2012
Bolcom, William.
0074 Aa 2; UAl
William Bolcom is a composer and pianist. Joan Morris is a mezzo-soprano. They are both members of the University of Michigan School of Music faculty. Bolcom and Morris have given numerous performances since 1971. They have also recorded albums of classical and popular songs. Performance files include programs, itineraries, newspaper articles and reviews of each performance, and contracts. There are also files relating to University of Michigan student production of Mina & Colossus; original scores to Bolcom's compositions, including McTeague, Casino Paradise, and A View from the Bridge; and topical files relating to awards, competitions, and other activities and interests.
60.5 linear feet in 73 boxes including oversize
31 bundles
1 oversize folders
3 oversize posters
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated by William Bolcom and Joan Morris (donor no. 8877 ) in multiple accessions beginning in 1999.
The collection is open for research.
William Bolcom, born in Seattle, Washington in 1938, has been recognized as one of America's most significant composers and pianists. He began piano study at the age of five. He later studied composition with John Verall, giving piano recitals throughout the Northwest before entering the University of Washington as a private student of composition, continuing his studies with Verall, and piano, with Berthe Poncy Jacobson. He received his B.A. from the University of Washington in 1958. Further studies followed with Darius Milhaud at Mills College and at the Paris Conservatory of Music. Bolcom received his doctorate from Stanford University in 1964. In the early sixties his serious compositions reflected the influence of Stockhausen, Berio, and Boulez, while at the same time he was writing theater music, most notably the 1961 off-Broadway hit The Red Eye of Love and his 1962 Dynamite Tonite, written with Arnold Weinstein, which received an American Academy of Arts and Letters Award. The late sixties saw a shift in his focus to ragtime and American music. He composed and performed rags throughout the country, meeting mezzo-soprano Joan Morris, who shared his interest in the American vernacular, in 1972.
Joan Morris, born in Portland, Oregon in 1943, began voice study at the age of 19. She attended Gonzaga University in Spokane prior to studies at the American Academy of Dramatic Arts in New York on an ABC scholarship. There she studied with Clifford Jackson and Federica Schmitz-Svevo. As a performer, she toured for two years with the Whit/Lo Singers, starred Off-Broadway in The Drunkard, and performed with harpist Jay Miller. Following her meeting with Bolcom in 1972, the two began giving concerts of American song throughout the United States, Canada, and Europe. Bolcom and Morris were married in 1975.
As champions of the American popular vocal literature, Bolcom and Morris perform songs from the late 19th century through the 1920s and 1930s, as well as cabaret songs written by Bolcom and poet-lyricist Arnold Weinstein. They have performed in Istanbul, Cairo, Moscow, and London, as well as notable venues throughout the United States, and have appeared on several television programs. Since his collaboration with Morris, Bolcom has continued to compose a vast repertoire of symphonies, concertos, operas, chamber music, songs, choral music and piano compositions, including the score to John Tuturro's film Illuminata and the music for Arthur Miller's play, Broken Glass. Compositions from every stage of Bolcom's career have earned him numerous honors, including awards from BMI, two Guggenheims, several Rockefeller Foundation and National Endowment for the Arts awards and grants, and two Koussevitsky Foundation Awards. In 1988 he received a Pulitzer Prize for Music for his Twelve Etudes for Piano. Morris has performed in many of Bolcom's stage productions, including The Beggar's Opera and Casino Paradise, and as a soloist in Bolcom's premiers of Songs of Innocence and of Experience and his Fourth Symphony, which was recorded in 1988 and which received two Grammy nominations.
Together, Bolcom and Morris have recorded twenty albums. The first After the Ball, resulted in a Grammy nomination for Morris for best vocal soloist performance on a classical album. Other discs include collections of cabaret songs, and the songs of Cole Porter, the Gershwins, Berlin, Rodgers and Hart, and Kern, as well as the songs of Vincent Youmans.
Bolcom has taught composition at the University of Michigan School of Music since 1973, and has been a full professor since 1981. In 1977 he received the Henry Russel award, the highest academic prize given by the University. In the fall of 1994 the University named him the Ross Lee Finney Distinguished University Professor of Music. He has also received the Michigan Council for the Arts Award from the State of Michigan, and Honorary Doctor of Music Degrees from the San Francisco Conservatory and Albion College. Morris has taught courses in voice and musical theater with the University since 1981.
The papers of William Bolcom and Joan Morris document his work as composer and performer and is collaboration with Joan Morris in performance and recording of American popular songs and classical music. There is some material relating to their academic work at the University of Michigan, notably a 1988 production of a student opera Mina & Colossus. The papers include programs, itineraries, and correspondence relating to performances, manuscript and published scores, topical files, several sound recordings, and photographs. The collection is divided into four series: Performances (1971-2010), Mina & Colossus (1998), Scores (1960-2006) and Topical (1977-1997).
Subjects:
Bolcom, William.; Composers--United States.; Mezzo-sopranos--United States.; Morris, Joan, 1943-; Music--Performance.; Pianists--United States.; University of Michigan--Faculty.Faculty.; University of Michigan. School of Music.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Bolcom, William.; Morris, Joan, 1943-
Contributors:
Morris, Joan, 1943-
Genre/Form:
Photographs.; Sound recordings.; Videotapes.
- Performances
  The Performances series includes performance programs, itineraries, correspondence sent or received at the time of the performance or pertaining to the performance itself, newspaper articles and reviews of the performance, and performance contracts. Photographs are scattered throughout the series. Additionally, at the beginning of each year is a folder containing calendars and planners kept by Bolcom and Morris during that year. At the end of each year (up to 1998), there is a folder (s) containing financial information about performances given that year, including expenses, earnings received, and often additional performance information. This information is divided by performance date. Of note within this series is the inclusion of the script and music written by Bolcom for Casino Paradise, performed June 7-21, 1992, and, as well as an audiocassette of a concert performed February 23/24/25, 1996.
  - 1971-1976 (Box 1)
  - 1977-August 7, 1980 (Box 2)
  - August 8/9, 1980-1983 (Box 3)
  - 1984-1986 (Box 4)
  - 1987-February 16, 1988 (Box 5)
  - February 18/19/20, 1988-February 5, 1989 (Box 6)
  - February 10/11, 1989-May 9, 1990 (Box 7)
  - May 10, 1990-September 15, 1991 (Box 8)
  - September 20, 1991-August 14/15, 1992 (Box 9)
  - September 12, 1992-November 13, 1993 (Box 10)
  - November 19, 1993-July 14, 1994 (Box 11)
  - August 19/20, 1994-May 22, 1995 (Box 12)
  - May 26, 1995-March 26, 1996 (Box 13)
  - April 14, 1996-December 1996 (Box 14)
  - 1997-February 10, 1998 (Box 15)
  - February 12, 1998-December 13, 1998 (Box 16)
  - January 1999-February 2000 (Box 37)
  - March 2000-November 2000 (Box 38)
  - November 2000-October 2001 (Box 39)
  - November 2001-October 2002 (Box 40)
  - October 2002-June 2003 (Box 48)
  - July 2003-May 2004 (Box 49)
  - May 2004-March 2005 (Box 50)
  - April-October 2005 (Box 51)
  - November 2005-October 2006 (Box 52)
  - November 2006-May 2007 (Box 53)
  - Miscellaneous later and unprocessed (Box 53)
  - May 2007-April 2008 (Box 61)
  - May 2008-February 2009 (Box 62)
  - March 2009-December 2009 (Box 63)
  - January 2010-March 2011 (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous earlier (Box 64)
  - Financial, 1998
    (prior to 1998 financial materials were interspersed with the Performance files)
    - Financial, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Financial, 1998 (Box 17)
      (continued)
  - Outsize performance posters, promotional photographs, citations, 1966-2012 (Box 73)
    (see also oversize folder UAl)
- Mina & Colossus (student play)
  The Mina & Colossus series is comprised of material relating to the 1998 University of Michigan student production of a musical entitled Mina & Colossus, which Morris produced. It includes correspondence relating to the planning and production of the play, funding and expense information, general production materials including programs and rehearsal schedules, information of the history and background of the play, publicity, website, and ticket information, and information about studio cast recording. Included in this series is Morris' copies of the production's script and songs, as well as audio-visual materials in the form of photographs, videos of the play and rehearsal process, and a cast recording on compact disc.
  - Correspondence
    - General (Box 17)
    - Carolyn Burke (Box 17)
    - Sam Davis and Ron Nyren (Box 17)
  - Funding and Expenses (Box 17)
  - General Production Materials (Box 17)
  - History and Background (Box 17)
  - Publicity, Website, Tickets (Box 17)
  - Recording Information (Box 17)
  - Scripts and Songs, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Compact disc: cast recording (Box 17)
  - Photographs: rehearsal and performance (Box 17)
  - Videos: rehearsal and performance (Box 18)
- Scores
  The Scores series is comprised of manuscripts and galley proofs with correction of Bolcom's work. Works of note include: McTeague (with libretto by Arnold Weinstein and Robert Altman), Casino Paradise (with libretto by Arnold Weinstein), A View from the Bridge (with libretto by Arnold Weinstein and Arthur Miller), A Wedding, and Songs of Innocence and of Experience. Some non-score material is found with these materials (such as librettos, notes, or correspondence).
  - Published, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - The Brooklyn Dodge, 1972 (Box 18)
  - The Canarsie Venus, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Conversations with Andre, 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Dedicace, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Epithalamium, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Fields of Flowers, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Frescoes (Box 18)
  - Fuga a Tre Voci, 1962 (Box 18)
  - The Gardenia (Box 18)
  - Night Pieces, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Nine Bagatelles, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Philippics, 1979 (Box 18)
  - McTeague
    - Manuscript and printed scores
      (includes some non-score material)
      - Manuscript and printed scores (Box 18)
      - Manuscript and printed scores (Box 19)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 1)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 2)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 3)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 4)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 5)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 6)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 7)
  - Casino Paradise
    - Manuscript and printed scores
      (includes audio cassette)
      - Manuscript and printed scores (Box 20)
      - Manuscript and printed scores (Box 21)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 8)
  - A View from the Bridge
    - Manuscript and printed scores (Box 22)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 9)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 10)
    - Printed scores (outsize) (Bundle 11)
  - A Whitman Triptych (Box 24)
  - A Whitman Triptych, 1 bundles (Bundle 29)
  - Cabaret Songs (Box 25)
  - Greatshot (Box 26)
  - Dynamite Tonight (Box 27)
  - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Box 28)
    (See also oversize folder (UAl) containing poster drawings based upon Blake’s engravings for performance at the First United Unitarian Church of Ann Arbor; also three oversize posters of Blake’s original engravings from the Hill Auditorium production signed by Bolcom and others. The titles of the Blake engravings were “Infant Sorrow,” “The Clod and the Pebble” and “Nurses Song.”)
  - Songs of Innocence and of Experience, 7 bundles
    - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Bundle 12)
    - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Bundle 13)
    - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Bundle 14)
    - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Bundle 15)
    - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Bundle 16)
    - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Bundle 17)
    - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Bundle 18)
  - Fifth Symphony, 1 bundles (Bundle 19)
  - Sixth Symphony, 1 bundles (Bundle 20)
  - Three Delgado Palacios Dances, 1 bundles (Bundle 21)
  - Gaea, 1 bundles (Bundle 22)
    (see also Boxes 32 and 70)
  - MCMXC Tanglewood, 1 bundles (Bundle 23)
  - Delicias; a suite of dances ..., 1997; 1 bundles (Bundle 24)
  - Orphee Serenade, 1 bundles (Bundle 25)
  - Clarinet Concerto, 1 bundles (Bundle 26)
  - Seventh Symphony: A symphonic Concerto, 1 bundles (Bundle 27)
  - A Gentle Little Fanfare, 1 bundles (Bundle 28)
  - Fourth Symphony, 1 bundles (Bundle 30)
  - Seattle Overture for orchestra, 2003; 1 bundles (Bundle 31)
  - Liberty Enlightening the World (Box 54)
  - Open House, 3 bundles (Box 54)
  - Fantasia Concertante for Viola ... in one movement, 1984-1985 (Box 54)
  - Bird Spirits for piano (Box 29)
  - The Canarsie Venus (Box 29)
  - Frescoes for 2 pianists (Box 29)
  - The Mental Traveler for piano (Box 29)
  - Night Pieces (Box 29)
  - Phantasmos, op. 1 (Box 29)
  - Reludes, Interludes, Postludes for organ (Box 29)
  - Rag-Tango, Homage to Ertnesto Nazareth (Box 29)
  - Raggin' Rudi for piano (Box 29)
  - Recuerdos ("Recreations") for 2 pianos (Box 29)
  - The Serpent's Kiss and Through Eden's Gates (Box 29)
    (also in oversize box 30)
  - A 60-second ballet (for chickens) (Box 29)
  - Sonata for 2 pianos (Box 29)
  - Sonatina for piano (Box 29)
  - Terminaison de "Navarra" d'Isaac Albeniz (Box 29)
  - Three Classical Rags (Box 29)
  - Three Popular Rags
    - Seabiscuits (Box 29)
    - Tabby Cat Walk (Box 29)
    - Last Rag (Box 29)
  - Three Dance Portraits for piano
    - The Dead Moth Tango (Box 29)
    - Knock-stuck (Box 29)
    - Abracadabra (Box 29)
  - Three Rags
    - The Poltergeist (Box 29)
    - Graceful Ghost (Box 29)
    - Incineratorag (Box 29)
  - 12 Etudes for piano (Box 29)
  - 12 New Etudes for piano (Box 29)
  - The Water Hen (Box 29)
  - Early compositions and sketches, 1950s (Box 29)
  - Fantasy-Sonata for piano, 1961-1962 (Box 30)
  - Various Fantasies (Box 30)
  - Introduction and Waltz (Box 30)
  - 12 New Etudes for piano (Box 30)
  - Rag collection (Box 30)
  - The Serpent's Kiss (Box 30)
  - Briefly It Enters (Box 31)
  - Camp Shadywillow (Box 31)
  - The Digital Wonder Watch (Box 31)
  - Fanfare for a New President (Box 31)
  - I Will Breathe a Mountain (Box 31)
  - Let Evening Come (Box 31)
  - Lime Jello Marshmallow Cottage Cheese Surprise (Box 31)
  - Maray (Box 31)
  - The Mask (Box 31)
  - The Mirale (Box 31)
  - Night, Make My Day (Box 31)
  - Three Donald Hall Songs (Box 31)
  - Tillinghast Duo (Box 31)
  - Tillinghast songs (Box 31)
  - Turbulence-A Romance (Box 31)
  - Lyric Concerto for Flute and Orchestra, 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - Gaea (Box 32)
    (see also oversize bundle no. 22 and Box 70)
  - Capriccio (in four movements), 1985 (Box 32)
  - Spring Trio; a Bouquet of Traditional Flower Rags, 1996 (Box 32)
  - Medusa, 2002 (Box 32)
  - Duets for Quintet (Box 32)
  - Whisper Moon (Box 32)
  - A Wedding, Act II (Box 33)
  - A Wedding, Act II (Box 34)
  - A Wedding, Act II (Box 35)
  - A Wedding, Act II (Box 36)
  - Ancient Cabaret, 2001 (Box 41)
  - Black Host, 1967 (Box 41)
  - Celestial Dinner Music, 1996 (Box 41)
  - Concerto-Serenade, 1964 (Box 41)
  - Convergin on the Mountain, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Décalage, 1961-1962 (Box 41)
  - Fairytales, 1987-1988 (Box 41)
  - FiveFoldFive, 1985-1987 (Box 42)
  - Four Preludes on Jewish Melodies, 2005 (Box 42)
  - The Garden of Eden (arranged for 2 pianos in 2005) (Box 42)
  - Gospel Preludes (Box 42)
  - The Graceful Ghost, 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - Hydraulis, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Le fantome du Clavecin, 2005 (Box 43)
  - Lilith, 1984 (Box 43)
  - May-Day, 2002 (Box 43)
  - Mysteries, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Nine New Bagatelles, 2005 (Box 43)
  - The Rhodora, 2000 (Box 44)
  - Serenata Notturna, 2005 (Box 44)
  - Sextet, 1960 (Box 44)
  - Spring Trio, 1996 (Box 44)
  - Suite No. 1 in C minor, 1994-1995 (Box 44)
  - Symphony no. 2 {Oracles}1962-196 (Box 44)
  - Terminaison de "Navarra" d'Isaac Albeniz, 1965 (Box 44)
  - Two Meditations on Poems of George Herbert, 2006 (Box 44)
  - Eighth Symphony, 2005 (Box 45)
  - Canciones de Lorca, 2006 (Box 46)
  - Canciones de Lorca, 2006 (Box 47)
  - Abendmusik (Box 55)
  - Ballade (Box 55)
  - Borborygm (Box 55)
  - The Brooklyn Dodge (Box 55)
  - Cabaret Songs (Box 55)
  - Collusions (Box 56)
  - Concerto for Clarinet and Orchestra (Box 56)
    (see also Box 70)
  - Concerto Grosso for Saxophone Quartet and Orchestra (Box 56)
  - Duets for Quintet (Box 57)
  - Duo Fantasy (Box 57)
  - Eighth Symphony (Box 57)
  - Field of Flowers (Box 57)
  - First Symphony for Band (Box 57)
  - First Violin Sonata (Box 57)
  - Four Piedmont Choruses (Box 58)
  - The Garden of Eden (Box 58)
  - Knight Hubert (Box 58)
  - La fantome du clavecin (Box 58)
  - Let Evening Come (Box 58)
  - Lyric Concerto (Box 58)
  - Navarra [completion of Albeniz piece] (Box 59)
  - Octet: Double Quartet (Box 59)
  - Orphée-Sérénade (Box 59)
    (see also Box 68)
  - Piano Quartet (Box 59)
  - Piano Quintet (Box 59)
  - Seasons (Box 60)
  - Seattle Slew sketches, circa 1986 (Box 60)
  - Seventh Symphony (Box 60)
    (see also Box 72)
  - Song for Band (Box 60)
  - A Song for St. Cecilia's Day (Box 60)
  - Songs of Innocence and of Experience (Box 60)
  - Violin Concerto (Box 60)
  - Yet Another Goldberg Variation (Box 60)
  - Billi in the Darbies, 2009 (Box 68)
  - Broadside for, 1983 (Box 68)
  - Eleventh String Quartet, 2002 (Box 68)
  - Fourth Violin Sonata, 1994 (Box 68)
  - Fourth Violin Sonata, 1996 (Box 70)
  - Hawthorne Tree, 2009 (Box 68)
  - Orphée-Sérénade, 2009 (Box 68)
    (see also Box 59)
  - Second Piano Quintet, 2010-2011 (Box 69)
  - Sonata for Violoncello and Piano, 1989 (Box 69)
  - Tenth String Quartet, 1988 (Box 69)
  - Third Sonata for Violin and Piano (Sonata Stramba), 1992 (Box 69)
  - Trio for Clarinet, Violin and Piano, 1993 (Box 69)
  - Concerto for Clarinet and Orchestra, 1988 (Box 70)
    (See also Box 56)
  - Gaea, 1995 (Box 70)
    (See also Box 32 and oversize bundle no. 22)
  - Lyric Concerto, 1992-1993 (Box 70)
    (See also Box 58)
    (includes Impromptu, 1960)
  - Ninth Symphony, 2011 (Box 71)
  - Seventh Symphony, 2002 (Box 72)
    (See also Box 60)
  - Spring Concerto, 1986-1987 (Box 72)
- Topical files
  The Topical series is comprised of 1 linear ft. of materials relating to subjects such as general correspondence, honorary degree ceremonies, and public events in which Bolcom and Morris participated which do not constitute performances. This series includes an eleven year run of records pertaining to Bolcom and Morris' record company, Elektra/Asylum/Nonesuch.
  - Accounting statements, 1986-1994 (Box 23)
  - Albion College Honorary Degree Convocation, 1995 (Box 23)
  - CBC Union Boycott, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1997 (Box 23)
  - Elektra/Asylum/Nonesuch, 1982-1992; 11 folders (Box 23)
  - Gerald R. Ford commemorative dedication program, 1981 (Box 23)
  - ICM Artists, 1990-2008 (Box 23)
  - Michigan Theatre Budget Information, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
  - Music Lovers' Calendar, 1992 (Box 23)
  - San Francisco Conservatory of Music Honorary Degree Commencement Exercises, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Seminar Series for Women of Michigan, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Sonidas de las Americas Festival, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Van Cliburn International Piano Competition, 1997 (Box 23)
  - William Albright scores and miscellaneous (Box 23)
- Videotapes
  - Bolcom & Morris, Sorg Opera House, Middletown, OH, September 14, 1985 (Box 65)
  - William Bolcom at the Scott Joplin Ragtime Festival, June 1993 (Box 65)
  - Hazen and Rusty 40th Anniversary Party, September 25, 1994 (Box 65)
  - Bolcom & Morris OBIE Awards, May 22, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM); 1 optical disks DVDs (Box 65)
  - Bolcom & Morris at the Gilmore, Kalamazoo Civic Auditorium, April 28, 1998; 1 videotapes VHS (TM); 1 optical disks DVDs (Box 65)
  - Bolcom & Morris, White Barn Theatre (Box 65)
  - Beverley J. Pooley Memorial Service, Lydia Mendelssohn Theatre, October 21, 2001; 1 hour 24 minutes (Box 65)
  - Bolcom & Morris perform cabaret songs at the Flea Theater, September 7, 2003; 3 videotapes (Box 65)
    (different camera set-ups)
  - Bolcom & Morris at the Flea Theater, September 14, 2003; 3 videotapes (Box 65)
  - Bolcom & Morris at the Flea Theater, September 21, 2003; 2 videotapes (Box 65)
  - Kerrytown Concert House 20th Anniversary Concert, October 2004; 1 videotapes VHS (TM); 1 optical disks DVDs (Box 65)
- Sound recordings
  - Audio-cassettes
    - With Clifford Jackson, Hollins College in VA, I-A, November 1973 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - With Clifford Jackson, Hollins College in VA, II-A, November 1973 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Gershwin Songs, Ann Arbor, September 15-17, 1975 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Gershwin, George: 16 songs, Nonesuch, July 1978 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - The Italian Lesson, July 6, 1980 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - American Brass Quintet, B & M II, July 6, 1980; July 7, 1980 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Fort Worth, October 29-30, 1981 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Music in America, Gershwin Salute, October 1983 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Paul Jacobs Concert, February 24, 1984 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Cleveland Concert, Museum of Art, September 19, 1984 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Irving Berlin Songs, June 1985 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Irving Berlin Songs, July 31, 1985 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Cabrillo, Prelude Concert, July 1986 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Lime Jello, Levittown, PA, 1987 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Kennedy Center, Gershwin, I, September 30, 1987 (Box 66-1)
    - Kennedy Center, Gershwin, II, September 30, 1987 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Kennedy Center, September 30, 1987 (Box 66, Item 1)
    - Town Hall, NYC presents I, October 12, 1987 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Town Hall, NYC presents II, October 12, 1987 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Weill Hall, #3, October 16, 1987 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Spring Break Spots (2), 1988 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Tribute to Berlin, High Performance, February 10, 1988 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - UMASS #1, May 5, 1988 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - UMASS #2, May 5, 1988 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Cole Porter, Revised, July 3, 1988 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - University of North Texas, October 8, 1988 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Mohawk Trail Series, July 1, 1989 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Aspen Music Festival, July 22, 1989 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Aspen Music Festival, August 11-12, 1989 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Madison, October 7, 1989 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Let's Do It, Aspen, November 14, 1989 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Carleton College, January 19, 1990 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Columbia, MD, June 23, 1990 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Fascinatin' Rhythm Series, November 10, 1990 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Desert Island Discs, December 15, 1990 (Box 66, Item 2)
    - Memphis State University, New Music Festival, February 16, 1991 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - WCW, March 2, 1991 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Composer's Union Hall, Moscow, June 6, 1991 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Cole Porter 100th, Carnegie Hall, I, June 9, 1991 (Box 66, Item 3)